Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XCVI. 1939 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 475-153. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 153
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide for Minimum Annuity, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 475-154. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 154
    - 40-Hour Week, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 475-155. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 155
    - Contributory Pensions, Canadian Pacific Railway, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 475-156. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 156
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Provide Disability Annuity After 15 Years' Service, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 475-157. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 157
    - Taxation of Labor-Saving Devices, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 475-158. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 158
    - Federal Workmen's Compensation Act, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 475-159. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 159
    - Neutrality, Profits of War, Conscription of Wealth, and Protection of Rights of Labor, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 475-160. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 160
    - Legal Holidays, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 475-161. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 161
    - One Day in Seven of Rest, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 475-162. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 162
    - Furloughed Employees, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 475-163. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 163
    - Time and One-Half for Sunday Work, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 475-164. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 164
    - Bidding on Positions Bulletined in Other Seniority District, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 475-165. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 165
    - Printing Express Agreement, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 475-166. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 166
    - Drivers Passing Through Picket Lines, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 475-167. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolutions Nos. 167 and 167a
    - Election of Board of Adjustment by Referendum, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 475-168. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 168
    - Passenger Conductors Doing Clerical Work, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 475-169. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 169
    - Mileage Base For Express Messengers, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 475-170. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 170
    - Prohibit Quitting Time Between Midnight and 5:00 am, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 475-171. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 171
    - Credit Unions. 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 475-172. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 172
    - Expenses of Express Messengers Away From Home, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 475-173. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 173
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Penalize Persons Remaining in Service After 65 Years of Age, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 475-174. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 174
    - Use of Percentage Division Basis for Less-than-Carload Traffic, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 475-175. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 175
    - General Chairmen to Be Delegates to Convention, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 475-176. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 176
    - Vacations. 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 475-177. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 177
    - 5-Day Week, 1939-1940 (Box 608b, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 475-178. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 178
    - General Chairmen to Be Delegates to Convention, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 475-179. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 179
    - Ritual for Installation of Officers, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 475-180. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 180
    - Monument to Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, Sedalia, Missouri, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 475-181. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 181
    - Pass Privileges for Employees of Camden Warehouse, Inc., 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 475-182. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 182
    - Colored Employees, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 475-183. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 183
    - Jurisdiction Dispute Between Brotherhood and Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 475-184. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 184
    - International Labor Organization Endorsed, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 475-185. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 185
    - Colored Employees, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 78)
    - Colored Employees, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 79)
    - Colored Employees, Insurance, 1939-1941 (Box 608b, Folder 80)
    - Colored Employees, 1939-1945 (Box 608b, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 475-186. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 186
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to Credit Furlough Time, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 475-187. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 187
    - Railroad Retirement Act, Cupples Station, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 475-188. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 188
    - Appreciation Expressed to City of Toronto and Committee on Arrangements, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 475-189. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 189
    - Appreciation Expressed to Express Agency for Free Transportation Furnished Delegates, 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 475-190. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 190
    - Appreciation Expressed for Courtesies Extended to Delegates by Various Individuals and Organizations., 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 475-191. 1939 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 191
    - Passing of Gray, C.R., 1939 (Box 608b, Folder 87)